Look, I-I admit it, I may
have crossed a line here,
(Leonard:)but come on, Raj, your
sister is a grown woman,
and to her, I'm a forbidden
piece of white chocolate.
(Raj:)I don't believe it.
(Raj:)This is a terrible
betrayal of my trust.
No, w-w-would it
help if I told you
(Leonard:)that I offered her my heart,
and she kind of stomped on it?
(Raj:)How hard did she stomp?
(Leonard:)Very hard.
(Raj:)Okay, I'm good.
(Howard:)Well, Raj,
(Howard:)I just want to say that I'd
never betray your trust.
(Howard:)Unlike Leonard,
I respect you.
(Leonard:)Really?
Mm-hmm.
(Leonard:)Was it out of respect
that you didn't tell Raj
(Leonard:)about the time you dropped
his iPhone in a urinal?
Dude, I put that thing
on my face!
(Sheldon:)I think a more amusing
violation of Raj's trust
(Sheldon:)is when Howard convinced him
that foreigners give presents
(Sheldon:)to Americans
on Thanksgiving.